This is a simplified and shortended version of how a real world script might look like.
It is meant as a simple “crash test” to detect if commits accidentally break some common things, but it's not exhaustive.
Unlike regression test, the important thing
here is not to avoid changing the rendering
in an undesirable way, but just to not fail or
crash when processing and rendering this
script.
Some shapes
for title
Now opening (without karaoke tags)
with some janky workaround instead of @font
soredemo bokura ha susumu darou
tsumetai namida ga hou wo nurashi demo
saku hana ha fuyu wo shiru
daijoubu soba ni iru
「That's a promise forever.」
mune ni nagare yuku 「melody」
kimi to utai, tsuzukeru 「symphony」.
Dialogue
_Type_
Internal Dialogue
Dialogue 2: now with extra text
Second Speaker
Some Sign:
And the text that is written
on it. With some rotation.
Moar Dialogue
And for ending
(with actual karaoke,
and a manual text background)
I'll shower in the sunshine.
Happy Monday.
笑えば 空まで「shining」。
waraeba sora made「shining」。
Let's chill out it's comfy time,
our after school.
この 時間が 何より「bright」。
kono jikan ga nani yori「bright」。
NEXT EPISODE
Never
ciao
empty
EMPTY