Efect: Banner, delay=0
This is the actual text which will be displayed as a subtitle onscreen. Everything after the 9th comma is treated as the subtitle text, so it can include commas.
Effect: Scroll up, delay=0 - to 90 (PlayResY)
Effect: Scroll down, delay=0 - to 90 (PlayResY)
This is the actual text which will be displayed as a subtitle onscreen. Everything after the 9th comma is treated as the subtitle text, so it can include commas.
Efect: Banner, delay=25
Effect: Scroll up, delay=25 - to 90 (PlayResY)
This is the actual text which will be displayed as a subtitle onscreen. Everything after the 9th comma is treated as the subtitle text, so it can include commas.
Effect: Scroll down, delay=25 - to 90 (PlayResY)